{
    "id": "9bc34daa962244b4b1c23023c093a46b",
    "title": "Countable And Uncountable Nouns Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Could you pass me ……………………? I have spilled some juice on the floor.",
            "description": "A cloth is a piece of material used for cleaning.",
            "answers": [
                "a cloth",
                "a clothing",
                "a clothe"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I must buy ……………………………",
            "description": "Clothes does not have a singular form. We say a piece of clothing.",
            "answers": [
                "a clothing",
                "a clothe",
                "a piece of clothing"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The poor man was arrested for stealing ………………………….",
            "description": "Bread is uncountable in English. The countable equivalents are a piece of bread / a loaf.",
            "answers": [
                "a bread",
                "a loaf"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "How ………………………. money do you earn in a week?",
            "description": "Money is uncountable in English and hence it is used with much.",
            "answers": [
                "much",
                "many",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "A ………………………….. struck the building.",
            "description": "Lightning is uncountable. The countable equivalent is a flash of lightning.",
            "answers": [
                "lightning",
                "piece of lightning",
                "flash of lightning"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I have got ………………………… to do.",
            "description": "Work is uncountable. ",
            "answers": [
                "much work",
                "many works"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I was held up by ………………………..",
            "description": "Traffic is uncountable. It does not have a plural form.",
            "answers": [
                "a traffic",
                "the traffic",
                "the traffics"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Politics ………………………. a dirty game.",
            "description": "Politics is usually considered as a singular noun.",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "In my opinion, too much mathematics ………………………. taught in schools.",
            "description": "Mathematics is usually considered as a singular noun.",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "We are all eager to increase our ……………………………",
            "description": "Knowledge does not have a plural form.",
            "answers": [
                "knowledge",
                "knowledges"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Six people lost their ……………………… in the accident.",
            "description": "To talk about several people doing the same thing or the same thing being done to several people, we normally use the plural form of the noun.",
            "answers": [
                "life",
                "lives"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Her ……………………….. very curly.",
            "description": "Hair is uncountable in English.",
            "answers": [
                "hair is",
                "hairs are"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}